CURRICULUM VITAE

Jefferson T. Yarbah

SUMMARY:

I am young, hardworking; highly motivated and blessed with excellent Information & Communications Technology as well as Computer Science and Applications knowledge with experience. I am dedicated to every assigned task with the mentality of continuous improvement and humility.

PERSONAL INFORMATION:

Date of Birth : December 29th 2000

Place of Birth : Greenville City, Sinoe County

Nationality : Liberian

Phone : +91-636-136-9495/+231-778-125-665

Email : <u>Jeffersonyarbah123@gmail.com</u>

Marital Status : Single

EDUCATIONAL BACKGROUND:

2021-Present : Bachelor of Computer Application (BCA) candidate,

Reva university, India 2024 Batch

2014-2019 : Bachelor of Information Technology(BIT)

with concentration In System Administration Starz University, Sinkor-Monrovia Liberia

2013-2014 : High School Certificates/Diploma / WAEC Certificate

Bassa High School System, Buchnan City

Grand Bassa County, Liberia

WORKING EXPERIENCE

2019-2020 : SchoolWeb Manager/Secretary/Assist. Registrar

Love International Preparatory School

Matadi, Airfield Sinkor

Monrovia Liberia

Description:

- -Manage School Web
- -Monitor students' activities daily
- -Alert parents with students' progress marks through email and sms
- -Crate Staffs Monthly Payroll
- -Assist Registrar by Tracking Fees Payment
- -Manage the entire school documents such as Diplomas, Certificates, Transcripts, Letters and Tests Printing.

2018-2019 : Instructor (Computer Science)

DRIMS School System

Lakpazee, Airfield Sinkor

Monrovia Liberia

Description:

- -Working encyclopedia of students in the class room
- -Investigator of student's activities in class/on campus
- -Evaluator of effectiveness of students' activities in the class room
- -Moral Builder of student's behaviors
- -Performed an effective maintenance of the computer lab, providing hardware services and software solutions

2018-2019 : Instructor (Computer Science)

Barnes Foundation School System

Lakpazee, Airfield-Sinkor

Monrovia Liberia

Description:

- -Manage the entire school documents such as Diplomas, Certificates, Transcripts, Letters and Tests Printing.
- -Ensured effective maintenance of the 8th Grade Class, served as sponsor.
- --Performed an effective maintenance of the computer lab, providing hardware services and software solutions

REFERENCES:

Mr. John D. Gbartea Former Principal, Barnes Foundation School (2014 - 2018) Airfield-Sinkor, Monrovia Liberia Contact: 0777-619-089

Mr. Abraham Kekula Principal, DRIMS School System GSA Road, Payesville City Montserrado County, Liberia

Contact: 077-743-200